http://www.llewellyn.com/about/privacy_policy.php

Llewellyn Worldwide - About Us: Privacy Policy
X
OOPS!
VIEW CART
CONTINUE SHOPPING
X
ADDED!
VIEW CART
CONTINUE SHOPPING
X
OOPS!
MANAGE WISHLISTS
CONTINUE SHOPPING
X
ADDED!
CANCEL
Please wait while we add the items to your shopping cart...
(0)
Search Results
more results »
Your Wishlists
Wishlist (4)
My List (1)
Another List (2)
Subtotal:  $52.93 US
Llewellyn is committed to keeping our staff and customers healthy and safe,
as well as being good corporate citizens, during this time.
Click to read how we are responding to the COVID-19 pandemic.
New Worlds Catalog
New Worlds of Body, Mind & Spirit is Llewellyn Worldwide's consumer catalog.
Each issue offers valuable resources in a diverse range of subject material,
including Witchcraft & Paganism, Tarot & Divination, Magick & Shamanism,
Alternative Health & Self-Help, and more » read more
On Sale Now!
Discover gorgeously illustrated annuals with all sorts
of helpful information to guide you through your year.
Horoscopes, Moon phases, weekly forecasts, herbal tips,
and more all wrapped up in easy-to-use guides!
Fill every day with a touch of magic!
Today's SPELL - World Homeless Day
It’s World Homeless Day, a day dedicated to reducing homelessness around the world. Today, create a prayer candle for Saint Benedict Joseph Labre, the patron saint of people who are homeless. (After his request to be a monk was refused several times, he released most of his possessions and lived on the streets of... » read more
A full year of guidanceand stunning imagery!
SHOP NOW
About Astrology
Browse All
Almanacs & Calendars
Getting Started
Houses & Aspects
Interpretive Techniques
Karmic Astrology
by Anna
Readers, please enjoy this guest blog post by Wendell C. Perry, author of the new Behind the Horoscpe.
I never thought of myself as a political person, but looking over my blog (at goodgollyastrology.com), I have to admit that in recent years the subject matter has become increasingly political.... » Read More
What's New
Order Your Copies Today!
SHOP NOW
About Body & Soul
Browse All
Health & Healing
Alternative Therapies
Auras
Chakras
Crystals & Gems
by Anna
Readers, please enjoy this guest blog post by Dr. Debbie Palmer, author of the new Mindful Beauty.
Summer—with its abundant fruits and vegetables—may be officially over, but fall's bounty is just as plentiful…and just as... » Read More
Browse All
Find Your Favorite Titles in Spanish
Almanacs & Calendars
Astrology
Body & Soul
Fiction
Gifts & Accessories
Magick
In Our Magick Blog
Join Us for Our First Llewellyn Virtual Author Forum: Ancestor Veneration!
by Anna
Join us for the first in our new Llewellyn Virtual Author Forum Series!
October 9, 2020—2pmCT
Join us for our first Llewellyn Virtual Author Forum! This bi-monthly series of free online roundtable events will feature your... » Read More
What's New
Order Your Copies Today!
SHOP NOW
About Nature-Based & Pagan
Browse All
Almanacs & Calendars
Ancestors & Ancestor Work
Animals & Mythical Creatures
Book of Shadows
Celtic & Druid
In Our Paganism Blog
Did You Miss Our Llewellyn Virtual Author Forum on Ancestor Veneration? Watch It Here!
by Anna
Today we hosted the first event in our new Llewellyn Virtual Author Forum Series!
The Llewellyn Virtual Author... » Read More
New Releases
SHOP NOW
FREE SPELL-A-DAY
Everyday spells for everyone!
About Supernatural & Parapsychology
Browse All
Paranormal
Ancient & Lost Civilizations
Ghosts & Hauntings
UFO & Alien Encounters
Vampires & Mythical Creatures
Parapsychology
by Anna
So many of us are stuck at home, looking for new sources of entertainment and learning. Why not try something new that may be out of your comfort zone?
Tarot is a deck of cards (usually 78) that can be used for any number of purposes,... » Read More
New Releases
Order Your Copies Today!
SHOP NOW
About Tarot & Divination
Browse All
» FREE Tarot Reading
Tarot Books
Advanced
Getting Started
Magic & Spells
Young Adult Titles Available Now
Order Your Copies Today!
SHOP NOW
AUTHORS
Authors Home
Browse Authors A-Z
Authors on Tour
Author Interviews
Author Articles
An Interview with Author Madame Pamita
Candles are simple but powerful additions to our magical workings. Here, The Book of Candle Magic author Madame Pamita discusses the easy, powerful, and fun of integrating candles into your magical workings....
READ MORE
On Tour Now
Online Clairvoyant Development Program
with Shannon Yrizarry
October 11, 2020
Inspired Conversations with Linda Joy
with Cyndi Dale
October 13, 2020
Use of Our Articles
Dealing with Emotional Tension: Discover Clarity for Tackling the Big Problems and Making the Big Changes
by Ann Todhunter Brode
The mandatory time out and social distancing of the past few months have given us an opportunity to look deep and evaluate what's working and what's not. Ann Todhunter Brode provides ways to help us...
READ MORE
More Articles
13 Candle Spell Hacks That Anyone Can Use9 Things to Keep On Your Ancestor AltarEssential Oils and the MoonYour Heavenly Entourage: How to Connect with Your Everyday Angels How to Use CBD Oil for Skincare
BLOGS
Browse Blogs by Subject
Astrology
Author News
Body & Soul
Magick
Paganism
Paranormal
Roundtable
Tarot
Other
Did You Miss Our Llewellyn Virtual Author Forum on Ancestor Veneration? Watch It Here!
by Anna
Today we hosted the first event in our new Llewellyn Virtual Author Forum Series!
The Llewellyn Virtual Author Forum is a bi-monthly series of free online roundtable events that feature your favorite Llewellyn authors discussing...
READ MORE
And There's More!
Join Us for Our First Llewellyn Virtual Author Forum: Ancestor Veneration!Learn Something NewFall's Healthiest Fruits and VegetablesAncestor Oracle Cards: Custom Divination with Your KinfolkMy Love of Pathworkings
ENCYCLOPEDIA
Encyclopedia Home
All Terms A - Z
Subjects
Popular Terms
Encyclopedia Articles
Popular Articles
Aa
Abracadabra
The spelling of the word was changed by Aleister Crowley to “Abrahadabra” to place the name Had, the second person of Crowley’s Thelemite trinity, at the center. Abracadabra is traditional...
READ MORE
Eleventh Degree
In the system of the O.T.O., this refers to a degree of the Order in which a person learns about using anal sex for sex magick. Some people have assumed that this is limited to sex magick as...
READ MORE
SUBSCRIBE
Subscribe
Current Issues
Archives
Astro Update
Monthly newsletter featuring informative astrology articles, useful tips, how new releases, and special sales offers.
e-Magazine
Newsletter featuring informative Llewellyn Journal articles, author interviews, useful tips, hot new releases, and special sales offers on all topics covered by Llewellyn.
Magick Update
Monthly newsletter featuring hot new releases, special sales offers, and informative articles and tips on all things magical, both high and low.
Paranormal Update
Monthly newsletter featuring informative paranormal articles, useful tips, hot new releases, and special sales offers.
Sales Alert
Sign up to receive announcements, information on the latest Llewellyn titles, and be notified when there is a website sale or special promotion.
Tarot Update
Monthly newsletter featuring informative tarot articles, useful tips, hot new releases, and special sales offers.
Wellness Update
Monthly newsletter featuring hot new releases, special sales offers, and informative articles and tips on emotional and physical wellness, holistic living and healing, and personal growth.
Witchy Update
Monthly newsletter featuring informative Wicca articles, useful tips, hot new releases, and special sales offers.
We have a newsletter for everyone! From Astrology to Witchcraft, we've got you covered with
monthly newsletters with articles, sales, new releases, and more. Click above links to subscribe
and browse our archives.
CONTACT
Contact Us
About Llewellyn
Llewellyn History
Careers at Llewellyn
Frequently Asked Questions
Imprints
Review Copies
For Booksellers
Welcome Booksellers!
Who's My Sales Rep?
International Sales
Trade Shows
Hurts/Remainders
Our Co-op Program
Our EDI Program
Our ONIX Title Feed
Bookseller Newsletters
Phone Numbers:
1-877-NEW-WRLD
1-877-639-9753
Local:	(651) 291-1970
Fax:	(651) 291-1908
Address:
Llewellyn Worldwide, LTD.
2143 Wooddale Drive
Woodbury, MN 55125
CustomerService@Llewellyn.com
Toggle navigation
About Us Menu
Home
About Us
Products
About Llewellyn
Table of Contents:
Our Commitment To Privacy
The Information We Collect
Information Provided When You Apply for a Job with Us
The Way We Use Information
About the Emails We Send
Credit Card Payments
Passively Collected Information
Our Commitment To Data Security
Our Commitment To Children's Privacy
How You Can Access or Correct Your Information
GDPR Right to Erasure
How To Contact Us
Our Commitment to Privacy
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our
online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected
and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where
personally identifiable information may be requested.
The Information We Collect:
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on any Llewellyn World website. On some pages,
you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information
collected at these pages are as follows:
Online Orders;
Name
Address
Email address
Phone number
Additional Information for our Online Business Customers;
Business Name
Fax
Business Type
Job Title
Federal Tax ID Number
State Tax ID Number
Business Website URL
Newsletters:
Email Address
First Name (optional)
Last Name (optional)
Astrology Reports — If you purchase an astrology report from us, we need to collect a combination of the following bits of information to complete your report;
Full name
Date of Birth
Birth City
Birth State
Birth County
Birth Country
Current Address - City, State, County, Country
On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order an astrology
report or a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient's
address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are:
Gifts sent directly to a third party;
Name
Address
Astrology Reports on a third party;
Full name
Date of Birth
Birth City
Birth State
Birth County
Birth Country
Current Address - City, State, County, Country
Information Provided When You Apply for a Job with Us:
When you apply for a job with us, we may collect your name, address, phone number, email address, education
level, salary requirements, previous work experience, references and other personal information about
your background and experience. We may also require electronic samples of your work.
The Way We Use Information:
We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order.
We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that
order.
We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product
and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent
necessary to complete that order.
We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to be used by our
sales and marketing departments. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals
visited a certain area on our website, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify
those individuals.
Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways
unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise
prohibit such unrelated uses.
About the Emails We Send:
We use a third-party email service, iContact, to send our email newsletters. While you will receive
transactional emails from us regarding the status of orders you place, no marketing email will
ever be sent to you without your express and deliberate opt-in to our email lists. Any information
you provide us, such as your email address, to contact you through iContact will be used only for
that purpose. iContact also complies with any and all regulations designed to protect user data.
View their privacy policy at
https://www.icontact.com/legal/privacy.
We also, at times, use a third-party service, OptinMonster, to collect email information.
You are never required to provide your name or email address if you do not wish to subscribe to our content.
Any information you provide us, including your name or email address, will be used to subscribe you to
the list(s) for which you have expressly asked to sign up. OptinMonster also complies with any and all
regulations designed to protect user data. You can view their privacy policy at
https://optinmonster.com/privacy/.
If ever you decide to opt-out of receiving marketing materials from us, there are links included
in every email that is sent to enable you to remove yourself from our list(s). You can also manage
your email contact preferences by emailing CustomerService@Llewellyn.com and indicate the email lists
from which you would like to be removed.
Credit Card Payments:
To pay for your order, you have the option to use a credit card.
We use a third-party credit card
collection and processing service.
At no time is your credit card information stored on our servers.
We cannot see your credit card number at all other than the last 4 digits as reported by this service
for verification purposes.
Passively Collected Information:
When you access our Sites, we automatically collect your computer or device's internet protocol (IP)
address and other technical information about your computer or device and website usage, such as your
browser type and version, time zone setting, and operating system and platform. This information is
only used to prevent malicious use of our websites and is regularly removed from our systems.
Our Commitment to Data Security:
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Our Commitment to Children's Privacy:
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or
maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website
is structured to attract anyone under 13.
How You Can Access or Correct Your Information:
You can access your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by sending
your request to;
Customer Service
Llewellyn Worldwide, LTD.
2143 Wooddale Drive
Woodbury, MN 55125
Please include your full name, current address, and a daytime phone number. We use this procedure to
better safeguard your information.
You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by logging into your account
on our website and updating the information or by sending us a request that credibly shows error.
To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity
before granting access or making corrections.
GDPR Right to Erasure (Right To Be Forgotten):
Article 17 of the European GDPR (General Data Protection Regulation) states that you have the right to
contact us and request that we remove your personally identifying information from our systems.
If you
would like us to forget who you are, please send your request to:
Customer Service - GDPR
Llewellyn Worldwide, LTD.
2143 Wooddale Drive
Woodbury, MN 55125
Please note that, if you are an author who is currently receiving royalties, we cannot forget who you
are until your rights have been returned and your contract is complete as we must retain your address in
order to send you your payments.
How to Contact Us:
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please visit the Contact Us
page of our website.
Effective
7/10/2019
IN OUR BLOGS
Did You Miss Our Llewellyn Virtual Author Forum on Ancestor Veneration? Watch It Here!
by Anna
Today we hosted the first event in our new Llewellyn Virtual Author Forum Series!
The Llewellyn Virtual Author Forum is a bi-monthly series of free online roundtable events that feature your favorite Llewellyn authors discussing topics...
READ MORE
What's New
The Tarot of Light
$34.95 US
/
Meditations for Children CD
$18.95 US
/
Copyright © 2020 - Llewellyn Worldwide, Ltd.
